[{"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #0", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30a6\u30a7\u30a4\u30bf\u30fc", "answer": "\u30a6\u30a7\u30a4\u30bf\u30fc - waiter"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #1", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u304a\u3058\u3044\u3055\u3093", "answer": "\u304a\u3058\u3044\u3055\u3093 - grandfather; old man"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #2", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5927\u4eba", "answer": "\u304a\u3068\u306a - adult"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #3", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5916\u56fd\u8a9e", "answer": "\u304c\u3044\u3053\u304f\u3054 - foreign language"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #4", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u697d\u5668", "answer": "\u304c\u3063\u304d - musical instrument"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #5", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7a7a\u624b", "answer": "\u304b\u3089\u3066 - karate"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #6", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30ab\u30ec\u30fc", "answer": "\u30ab\u30ec\u30fc - curry"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #7", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7740\u7269", "answer": "\u304d\u3082\u306e - kimono; Japanese traditional dress"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #8", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30b1\u30fc\u30ad", "answer": "\u30b1\u30fc\u30ad - cake"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #9", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5e83\u544a", "answer": "\u3053\u3046\u3053\u304f - advertisement"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #10", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7d05\u8336", "answer": "\u3053\u3046\u3061\u3083 - tea (black tea)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #11", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u8a00\u8449", "answer": "\u3053\u3068\u3070 - language"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #12", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30b4\u30eb\u30d5", "answer": "\u30b4\u30eb\u30d5 - golf"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #13", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30bb\u30fc\u30bf\u30fc", "answer": "\u30bb\u30fc\u30bf\u30fc - sweater"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #14", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u8c61", "answer": "\u305e\u3046 - elephant"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #15", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30d0\u30a4\u30aa\u30ea\u30f3", "answer": "\u30d0\u30a4\u30aa\u30ea\u30f3 - violin"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #16", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30d0\u30a4\u30af", "answer": "\u30d0\u30a4\u30af - motorbike"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #17", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7269\u4fa1", "answer": "\u3076\u3063\u304b - (consumer) prices"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #18", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u6587\u6cd5", "answer": "\u3076\u3093\u307d\u3046 - grammar"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #19", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5f01\u8b77\u58eb", "answer": "\u3079\u3093\u3054\u3057 - lawyer"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #20", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u52df\u96c6", "answer": "\u307c\u3057\u3085\u3046 - recruitment"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #21", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5e97", "answer": "\u307f\u305b - shop; store"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #22", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u3084\u304f\u3056", "answer": "\u3084\u304f\u3056 - yakuza; gangster"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #23", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7d04\u675f", "answer": "\u3084\u304f\u305d\u304f - promise; appointment"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #24", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u30ec\u30dd\u30fc\u30c8", "answer": "\u30ec\u30dd\u30fc\u30c8 - (term) paper"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #25", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u79c1", "answer": "\u308f\u305f\u304f\u3057 - I (formal)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #26", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u3046\u308c\u3057\u3044", "answer": "\u3046\u308c\u3057\u3044 - glad"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #27", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u60b2\u3057\u3044", "answer": "\u304b\u306a\u3057\u3044 - sad"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #28", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u8f9b\u3044", "answer": "\u304b\u3089\u3044 - hot and spicy; salty"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #29", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u53b3\u3057\u3044", "answer": "\u304d\u3073\u3057\u3044 - strict"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #30", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u8fd1\u3044", "answer": "\u3061\u304b\u3044 - close; near"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #31", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u3044\u308d\u3044\u308d", "answer": "\u3044\u308d\u3044\u308d - various; different kinds of"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #32", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5e78\u305b", "answer": "\u3057\u3042\u308f\u305b - happy (lasting happiness)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #33", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u3060\u3081", "answer": "\u3060\u3081 - no good"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #34", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7de8\u3080", "answer": "\u3042\u3080 - to knit"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #35", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u8cb8\u3059", "answer": "\u304b\u3059 - to lend; to rent"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #36", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u9811\u5f35\u308b", "answer": "\u304c\u3093\u3070\u308b - to do one's best; to try hard"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #37", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u6ce3\u304f", "answer": "\u306a\u304f - to cry"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #38", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u78e8\u304f", "answer": "\u307f\u304c\u304f - to brush (teeth); to polish"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #39", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u7d04\u675f\u3092\u5b88\u308b", "answer": "\u3084\u304f\u305d\u304f\u3092\u307e\u3082\u308b - to keep a promise"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #40", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u611f\u52d5\u3059\u308b", "answer": "\u304b\u3093\u3069\u3046\u3059\u308b - to be moved/touched (by ...)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #41", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u3044\u3089\u3063\u3057\u3083\u3044\u307e\u3059", "answer": "\u3044\u3089\u3063\u3057\u3083\u3044\u307e\u3059 - (someone honorable) is present/home"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #42", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5b9f\u306f", "answer": "\u3058\u3064\u306f - as a matter of fact, ..."}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #43", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5168\u90e8", "answer": "\u305c\u3093\u3076 - all"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #44", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e00\u65e5", "answer": "\u3044\u3061\u306b\u3061 - one day"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #45", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e8c\u65e5", "answer": "\u3075\u3064\u304b - two days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #46", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e09\u65e5", "answer": "\u307f\u3063\u304b - three days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #47", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u56db\u65e5", "answer": "\u3088\u3063\u304b - four days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #48", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e94\u65e5", "answer": "\u3044\u3064\u304b - five days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #49", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u516d\u65e5", "answer": "\u3080\u3044\u304b - six days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #50", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e03\u65e5", "answer": "\u306a\u306e\u304b - seven days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #51", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u516b\u65e5", "answer": "\u3088\u3046\u304b - eight days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #52", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u4e5d\u65e5", "answer": "\u3053\u3053\u306e\u304b - nine days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #53", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u5341\u65e5", "answer": "\u3068\u304a\u304b - ten days"}], "wrongAnswer": []}, {"type": "df", "background": "<p>What is the definition and pronunciation of the term?</p>", "course": "jpst200", "des": "ch13 #54", "qaPair": [{"question": "\u3088\u308d\u3057\u304f\u304a\u9858\u3044\u3057\u307e\u3059", "answer": "\u3088\u308d\u3057\u304f\u304a\u306d\u304c\u3044\u3057\u307e\u3059 - Thank you (in advance)"}], "wrongAnswer": []}]